Nathaniel Alexander

WEB DEVELOPER

Recent graduate with education and experience in web development. Highly poised and dedicated with talent in design principles and programming languages. Excellent eye for perfection in frontend functionality and design. As a recent graduate with an amazing and reliable work ethic, I am more than excited to start my career in the tech field.



(845) 763-6528



≥ natewerm2000@gmail.com



Las Vegas, NV



https://www.linkedin.com/in/nath aniel-alexander-934188196/

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE SUNY New Paltz 2021-2022

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE **Dutchess Community College** 2018-2020

Computer Repair/Computer Networking **Dutchess Boces CTI** 2016-2018

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

Proficient in

- HTML
- CSS/SCSS
- **Bootstrap**
- **Javascript**
- React
- Python
- Java
- Unreal Engine 4/5
- PHP
- MySQL

Competent in

- Vue.js
- MongoDB
- Node
- C++
- C#
- NumPy
- Blender

WORK EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEAD (Key Holder)

Sandbox VR, Las Vegas, NV | JUNE 2023 - present

Primary role as a Team Lead at Sandbox VR is to not only be responsible for opening and/or closing the store but ensuring all daily tasks are met, along with being communicative with the entire shift and making sure store operations are going smoothly with reservations and technology

- Open/Close store
- Maintain the Environment
- Health and Safety
- Shift Management
- Training and Job Mastery
- Deliver an Incredible Guest Experience
- Technical Support and Troubleshooting
- Collaboration

KEY HOLDER

Jo-ann Stores, Kingston, NY | NOVEMBER 2022 - JUNE 2023 Primary role as a key holder at this store was to open and close the store the day of my shift. I also had to ensure store functionality along with inventory management and provide a leadership role to team members.

- Open/Close store
- Measure and cut fabric
- Count register when opening and closing
- Provide excellent customer service to ensure satisfaction
- Handled shipments
- Inventory overstock discrepancy management
- Stock planograms and everyday freight shipments

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- Improving Efficiency
- Problem Solving
- Leadership and Training
- Attention to Detail
- Self teaching
- Team work
- Independent learning
- Reliability
- Motivated learner

INTERESTS

- Video Games
- Technology
- Personal Development
- Traveling
- Reading & Learning
- Long Distance Running
- Fishing
- Paintballing

WORK EXPERIENCE - Continued

KEY HOLDER

Just A Buck, Poughkeepsie, NY/Kingston, NY | MARCH 2021 – JUNE 2023 Primary role as a key holder at this store was to open and close the store the day of my shift. Not only did I have to ensure the store was opened/closed, I was responsible for ensuring the store was running smoothly. Along with providing tasks for the team members I am supervising and becoming a leader to the team.

- Open/Close store
- Create excellent displays when stocking
- Store operations and functionality
- Count registers
- Provide excellent customer service to ensure satisfaction
- Handled shipments
- Social media management

CASHIER

Just A Buck, Poughkeepsie, NY | July 2018 – March 2021 Primary role as a cashier is to assist customers at the check out and on the floor.

Ringing items, providing customer service, and stocking shelves were the main duties of this position

- Handled cash and card transactions with customers
- Count money in cash drawers at beginning of each shift
- Stocked shelves
- Provide excellent customer service to ensure satisfaction

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

GALACTIC CONQUEST

Unreal Engine 4 Video game C++/Blueprints Blender

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO

Personal portfolio of Nathaniel Alexander React, SCSS

Smart Library

SUNY New Paltz library HTML, CSS/Bootstrap, PHP, Python, MySQL, HikVision

Exercise App

Fitness app made in vue HTML, CSS/Bulma, JS, Vue.js, MongoDB